One, two, start!
(Red and white, you and your lover's unknowing love song, I wonder if I can sing it someday...)
Youth is like a hater, a drowning gaze, a courage that can't come out, blamed on the heat...
Wow, it's so beautiful!
The wood.
Heh.
It's coming out of a half-step.
Wow!
Oh, no! The costumes!
It's the station, my costume!
I'm so embarrassed! Let me try again!
Let me have a mature reaction!
It's probably on autopilot, but it's beautiful!
Oh, it's beautiful!
It's so beautiful!
Now you can zoom in!
New from 3 levels!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Your child's home...
It's this way!
New house?
Oh, my gosh!
Can I have Open the Door with you?
Yes! Yes, sir!
Open the door!
Oh, my gosh!
What?
That's great!
Good night.
Look, there's a TV.
TV?
Put your feet up here like this.
That's fun!
You can watch it like this.
This is home.
This is amazing.
I want to live here. Let's live here together in the future.
It's nice.
It's great. Let's live together.
We'll live together, right?
You'll have to pay the rent.
You're going to charge me rent.
It's really good.
You should try living here, too.
I don't mean come here.
Thank you for watching!
Next Episode
Rikoko-style, old-fashioned, rebellious religion.
Seriously ha~ to papa
radish to par
You're done
Please enjoy the special version of the picture here as well!
I'm the one stuck in the eye, imo
There are so many things happening today.
Here's one picture that makes it seem like everyone loves Ishiyama instead of him!
Look forward to the next time!
Good luck one day!
We are already closed today!
We're closed again today!
Matsuda, you were probably moving a lot!
Shika-chan!
Look at this.
Oh, I know, right?
Fun!
Yudane!
You guys!
I've been flying all this time.
It's fun!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
I'm gonna go take a bath.
It's okay, it's okay.
Ryu, go ahead.
Cute!
It's hard.
Oh, my God!
That's great.
Wow!
Too much?
It's delicious. It feels very midsummer.
Next time
There he is.
I can't reach this one either.
Hello.
Hey, guys, I'm here.
I'm holding a bug net.
Scary people.
Here he comes.
Here you go.
Can you hold it?
It's a little scary.
It's a little big.
Here comes the scary man.
It's big.
Like this one, which was totally out of place.
He's cute.
Nice tummy.
Nice and cute.Nice and cute.
Cute.
It's funny.
Okay, I think it's time we do this.
I'm mad, I'm mad, I'm mad.
Laughter.
Applause.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
My butt hurts.
Oh, really.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I want to stay the night.
And it even smells good.
Oh, yeah.
It's kind of scary in a way.
We're going to grill the meat.
Maybe. Burn it.
Oh, my God!
Sensation!
I could live without a bathtub.
Here's the care package.
Oh, I see.
The grooming thing.
I'll do my best.
Looks good.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum yum yum
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy
Looks good.
There's a guy eating it.
It's like someone says, "Here, I'll take a picture," and you take a picture.
I'll take a picture!
Yes, yes.
Okay, okay.
Mmm!
It's so good!
Yum!
Is this okay?
I'm so happy.
This is really good!
Bon appétit!
It's so cute!
I don't know...
It's cold!
Delicious!
In between beginner's shoots
I changed into my casual clothes
I'm eating like a normal person.
Serious BBQ
BBQ without worrying about the camera
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
It tastes even better than when we were filming!
Delicious!
I'm so glad they're grilling it for us!
Bon appétit!
Good morning!
I'd like to surprise Misato Matsuda when she wakes up from sleep!
What shall we do?
Good morning.
This is Ms. Misato Matsuda. She's sleeping, and I'd like to surprise her in her sleep.
I'm going to do a very cozy, royal surprise.
Good morning.
Milly, Milly, Milly.
Milly.
Sleep when you can.
Sleep when you can. Sleep a lot.
Millie.
I can sleep now.
Sleep a little more?
Millie.
In about five minutes.
They'll probably call the makeup artist.
Millie.
They're calling Millin.
There really is a bug.
It was an eye-opening surprise!
That's all for now.
Next time preview
There you go!
Here we go!
Here we go.
Let me take a look.
Amazing.
That's the calmest guy I've ever seen.
That's the one I couldn't see.
I'll be that one.
Oh, no.
Something.
Someone tell the mentor...
It's red.
Okay...
No, it's perfect.No, it's perfect now.
That felt good.
I don't have a tail. I don't have a tail.
It's round.
Perfect.
I don't think I've ever been to a candy store with a tail like this.
200 yen at a candy store.
That's expensive!
But it's only 100 yen!
Amazing!
That's amazing!
It's so good!
It's amazing!
Take another one.
Candy.
I want to buy this.
I love this.
Can I have a carrot?
Koppy Ramen
I love this!
The characters are cute.
I put it in.
I can at least eat the colored ones.
The ones that are sloppy
It's a drink.
And it melts.
Oh, I didn't get it.
I didn't get it.
It's not Amazon, it's... what was it?
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll throw it in the air.
Seino
It's not McClure.
Here we go.
Okay, let's do it.
Forget it.
This one's better.
It's so different from the hand.
It's just like my hand.
I've got it.
Where are you guys going?
Start the one-tube.
Cut.
Cut to one tube.
We're in the middle of a one-tube
End of one tube
Poo-poo
Oh no, oh no
Chita kita
This is a keeper if you finish getting dressed early.
Please don't.
You haven't changed.
I'm afraid this is where it's going to end up.
Mr. Sakamoto, you're still with us.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Yay!
September 8th.
Last look around already.
Ah, what the heck.
Sure thing.
Okay.
How did it go?
Well, I've always wanted to go out with the members.
I have an image of how much fun it was to have Christmas parties and gather together in the past, so I thought I'd like to try glamping at the end.
I wanted to try glamping, which is something I've always wanted to do, with everyone, so I decided to do it this time.
It was more fun than I thought it would be.
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
We did everything.
I know it was a bit like a rehearsal, but we were so busy today.
That's for sure.
Cut!
End of YouTube!
Pfft!